And look, I've been coaching men for
well over a decade, from special forces
some of the greatest rock bands in the
world.
And what I've learned is confidence is
not something you're going to think your
way to. It is something you have to
build with action.
So today I'm going to talk to you about
ways to actually build your confidence.
And it's not going to happen through
affirmations, right? We're going to have
get out into the real world and make
things happen.
one of the things in the context what
we're dealing with right now is women
women don't really care as much what you
say all they care about is how you make
them feel and one of the biggest
attraction markers for women when it
an energy exchange is is he confident is
he sure of himself has he been here
before does he know how this game this
interaction works And let's be honest, a
lot of guys know, right? We just haven't
had the reps. We haven't been to
batting cage and not to really get that
good swing down.
So you have to go get your at bats,
right?
With that energy exchange, you have to
give her this presence of one of the
things women need the most, which is
safety and security.
She has to feel what you're saying to
her. And all this comes from a grounded
place of.
confidence. So here's what I'm going to
give you today, guys.
Your challenge today is to go play the
compliment game.
A lot of guys that I work with do have a
hard time approaching women. They have
a hard time having conversations with
women. So what I want to do today is I
just want to get you used to having
conversations.
I want to get you used to just having
conversations, going up and talking to
somebody and saying, this is who I am.
Just want to come say, hey.
So here's how the compliment challenge
works.
I want you to just find the next five
people you interact with and just pay
a compliment.
Here's the caveat to this.
I don't want you to compliment something
about their physical attractiveness.
I want you to think outside the box here
because here's the magic.
Think about either a decision they had
to make or something that they had to
actually think about. It could be
something they're wearing. It could
You know, maybe she's got a purple
stripe in her hair.
Maybe she's got like, maybe she's got
some decorated Chuck keys on.
Maybe she's got like a Van Halen t
-shirt on.
Maybe she just got some great energy,
which by the way, leads me into my
one hack here.
If you ever don't know what to say to a
girl, just say, wow, you have amazing
energy. Watch what happens.
Guys, it's something in the way that
women receive that compliment. I promise
you, it lands and it works.
But you're having, like, you're just
going up to somebody and just giving
compliment. And here's what I also want
to remember. This is a non -outcome
-based compliment.
I don't want you thinking I have to give
this compliment and get something in
return. No, the point of this challenge
is to just go be a good human. Go change
five people's day.
And watch the energy exchange that
happens. Watch what happens when you
outcome off of the conversation.
Just go pay a compliment and watch how
that other person reacts.
Also, watch how much easier it gets for
you.
When you're not trying to land the
number, trying to land the date, and
not trying to get something out of that
person, all you're doing is trying to be
a good human and just go be a good guy.
When that's your sole goal, that
interaction becomes a lot easier.
And here's what I want you to do.
I want you to go find five people today
to go do that too.
Then I want you to make that a daily
habit.
That's just something deeply ingrained.
It kind of weirds my girlfriend out
because I do it so much.
But it's become a daily ingrained habit
in who I am right now.
I just pay compliments everywhere I go.
Hey, bro, look at your shoes, man.
Like, bro, how can I get in the gym like
you?
Or, wow, this coffee is absolutely
amazing. Did you make this?
Something as simple as that.
is what it's all about so that's your
challenge today guys go have as many of
those compliment challenge games as
possible i want to talk to you in the
upcoming videos about what to do after
that but i want you to get really good
this the number one thing that i hear in
feedback from guys doing this challenge
is people aren't so scary are they like
no they're human just like you i promise
you the people you're talking to are
probably just as insecure and scary as
are Go just pay compliments, be a good
human and watch how that changes your
confidence level and approaching people
moving forward. Because guys, we're
building confidence through action, not
through just thinking about it. So guys,
that's what I have for you today. That's
today's video.
I'm going to see you tomorrow where
we're going to talk about a little bit
of the growth mindset and how to reframe
things.
And that's just going to build upon what
we're doing today. So make sure you
take action today, guys.
Also, host in the community.
Give us feedback how this challenge
went. Let us know what happened when you
started paying confidence to people and
what happened in those interactions.
All right, guys, that's it. I'm Robbie,
and I'll see you tomorrow.