You know, I've been coaching men for over a decade,
from special forces to the best rock bands in the world,
and I've learned that confidence isn't earned through thoughts,
but through actions
. Today I'm going to talk to you about how to develop it.
And you're not going to get there with explanations, right?
You have to dive in and take charge.
One of the problems today is that women
don't care what you say.
What matters to them is how you make them feel.
And one of the most attractive qualities in women,
in this energy exchange, is confidence.
If you're confident, if you're experienced,
if you know how it works, how this interaction works—
and let's be honest, a lot of men have that, right?
We just didn't have the visual, right?
When I practice with the bat, I can't seem to hit it right.
So you have to take risks, right?
In this energy exchange,
you have to project that presence, something women crave more than anything.
It's about safety and security; they need to hear what you're saying.
And all of that comes from strong self-confidence.
That's what I'm offering you today.
Your challenge for today: Play the compliment game with men who...
Working men have a hard time approaching women.
They have a hard time talking to them.
My goal today is simply to get you into the habit of starting a conversation.
I want you to get into the habit of just making small talk.
Walk up to someone and say, "It's me, I just wanted to say hi."
That's how the compliment challenge works.
I want you to find the next five people.
When you interact with someone and give them a compliment,
I warn you: I don't want...
anything about their appearance.
I want you to think outside the box, but here's the thing:
think about a decision they had to make
or something they had to do. Think about it.
It could be something they're wearing, it could be,
you know, maybe I have a purple streak in my hair, uh, maybe.
Maybe I'm wearing custom Chuck Taylor shirts.
Maybe they have a Van Halen shirt, maybe they just have crazy charisma.
Which brings me back to the main point:
if you don't know what to say to a girl, simply say, "Wow, you have incredible charisma!"
Guys, look at the effect it has on women.
I assure you, it hits the nail on the head.
It's like
simply being with someone and giving them a compliment.
And I want to make one thing clear: it's not a compliment that expects something in return.
I don't want you to think I have to give this compliment and offer something in return.
No, the point of this challenge is simply to be a good person.
Change the lives of five people and observe the energy exchange that occurs.
Observe what happens when you remove any expectation of outcome from the conversation.
Approach someone, give them a compliment, and observe their reaction.
Also notice how easy it is when you don't try to calculate the value of the compliment.
You're just trying to have a good day without expecting anything in return.
You're simply trying to be...
a good person, a good guy, if that's your goal.
Interactions become much easier because of this, and that's exactly what I want from you.
I want you to find five people today to do this with.
Then, I want you to make it a daily habit; it's something that becomes ingrained.
My girlfriend doesn't seem to notice, huh? She does it a lot.
But for me, it's become a deeply ingrained daily habit, and it's an integral part of my personality.
I give compliments everywhere I go: "Hey, man, look at your shoes!" "
How can I, being your brother, go to the gym like you?"
"Wow, this coffee is amazing, right?"
It's that simple.
Here's your challenge for today:
play as many compliment games as you can.
In the next videos, I'll show you how.
But I really want to get good at it.
The first thing I see in the comments
is: "People do this challenge because they're not that intimidating, right?"
Well, no, they're just like you, I assure you.
The people you're talking to are probably just as shy and intimidating as you.
Compliment them.
Be kind, and you'll see how it will change their lives.
Their confidence and the way they approach others.
Trust is built through actions, not just thoughts.
That's all for today, that's all for this video.
We'll see you again tomorrow to discuss
growth mindset and how to reframe
things. This will build on what we've covered today.
So, take action today! Also, feel free to post in the community.
Share your thoughts on participating in this challenge.
Tell us what happened when you started paying attention
to others and what happened during those interactions.
That's all for today. I'm Robbie, and I'll see you tomorrow.